Register of the Wladyslaw Anders Collection, 1939-1946.
Hoover Institution Archives
Wladyslaw Anders Collection,
1939-1946
46004
Anders, Wladyslaw, 1892-1970
92 manuscript boxes, 17 card file boxes, 1 oversize box (44 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Orders, reports, card files, questionnaires, accounts, Soviet government documents and publications, photographs, microfiche, and printed matter, relating to World War II, the Polish Armed Forces in Russia, the Polish 2d Corps in Italy, Polish citizens arrested and deported under German and Soviet occupation, Polish foreign relations, the Polish government-in-exile in London, and Polish Jews. A digital copy of this entire collection is available at http://szukajwarchiwach.pl/800/1/0/-/.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
Alternative Form Available
Also available on microfilm (130 reels).
Digital copy in Poland's National Digital Archive at http://szukajwarchiwach.pl/800/1/0/-/. It was digitized from microfilm by the Polish State Archives.
Access Points
Poland. Polskie Sily Zbrojne. Armia polska na Wschodzie.; Poland. Polskie Sily Zbrojne. Armia polska w ZSSR.; Poland. Polskie Sily Zbrojne. Korpus, 2.; Soviet Union. Narodnyi komissariat vnutrennikh del.; Concentration camps--Soviet Union.; Forced labor--Soviet Union.; World War, 1939-1945.; World War, 1939-1945--Campaigns--Italy.; World War, 1939-1945--Deportations from Poland.; World War, 1939-1945--Poland.; World War, 1939-1945--Soviet Union.; Poland.; Poland--History--Occupation, 1939-1945.; Soviet Union.; Russia (Federation)
Introductory Note
The Wladyslaw Anders Collection is the core of the 1946 archival deposit to the Hoover Institution made by General Wladyslaw Anders, the Commander-in-Chief of the Polish Armed Forces. The collection is composed mostly of the archives of the Documents Bureau of the 2nd Polish Corps. The Bureau was established by General Anders in April 1943 to collect documentation on the 1939-1941 Soviet occupation of Eastern Poland, and the fate of the hundreds of thousands of Polish prisoners of war, labor camp inmates, and deportees, as well as to prepare materials in support of the Polish cause for the future peace conference.
The collection contains over 18,000 original personal accounts and questionnaires of former prisoners and deportees, some documents dating back to 1941, most completed later, shortly after the 1942 evacuation from the Soviet Union. The materials were once filed in one sequence numbered 1 to 18,304. Later the file was broken into two sections, one labeled as "Relacje" and the other as "Ankiety", translated loosely as "Statements" and "Reports" in the present Hoover register, but with the old numeration retained. The highest number of the "Reports" file is 15,714, and the highest number in the "Satements" file is 18,304. The "Statements" and the "Reports" files are complementary, with numbers which are lacking in one file found in the other. The documents have an alphabetical card index, occupying the first 34 boxes of the Anders Collection, comprised of over 18,000 cards, listing the name, brief biographical data, and the corresponding personal account or questionnaire number. The 18,000 plus documents contained in the next 33 boxes of the Anders Collection (boxes 35-68) represent a variety of formats. Two questionnaires, one shorter, page-long ten point form, and the second, a four-page questionnaire, were commonly used. There were also specialized questionnaires -for the clergy, for Jews, one about working conditions, etc. Some less typical materials, such as general situation reports, regional compilations, and memoirs, are also numbered with "Reports" and the "Statements". The personal accounts and questionnaires of the Anders Collection have a detailed subject index with about 250 entries on cards (boxes 89-92). There is also a card index (boxes 93-107) of several thousand names of people who died in prisons and labor camps or who were probably left behind after the 1942 evacuation to Iran. Additionally, the index includes the names of suspected collaborators and of Soviet camp and prison personnel. Besides the original accounts and questionnaires and the card indexes, the Anders Collection includes a large number of internal documents and reports collected or produced by the Documents Bureau (boxes 68-81). Finally, the Anders Collection is supplemented by materials generated by a 1951-1952 U.S. Government study of Soviet labor camps. During that time, with the permission of General Anders, the entire Anders Collection and some files of the Poland-Ambasada (Soviet Union) Collection, were loaned to the Library of Congress. In exchange, the Hoover Institution received copies of the resulting works -nearly 1,300 English language abstracts of the personal accounts from the Anders Collection (boxes 81-87), card indexes on the geography and terminology of the Soviet camp system (boxes 108-109), and a final report of the study.
Two other Hoover Institution collections include original depositions of Polish soldiers and civilians, former prisoners and deportees in the Soviet Union. These are the Poland-Ministerstwo Informacji i Dokumentacji Collection, and the Poland-Ambasada (Soviet Union) Collection. Most of the holdings of the Documents Bureau were filmed in 1945-1946 in Italy, before the transfer of the archives to the Hoover Institution. These microfilms are now part of the Col. Wincenty Bakiewicz Collection in the Archives of the Polish Institute and the Sikorski Museum in London. The personal papers of General Anders are also at the Polish Institute.
Maciej Siekierski
June 1998
Biographical Note
1892 Born
1919-1920 Served in the Polish-Russian War
1939 General Officer Commanding Ind. Cavalry Brigade
1939-1941 Taken prisoner by the Soviet Army and released
1941-1944 Commander-in-Chief of the Polish Armed Forces in the USSR
1944 Commander-in-Chief of the Polish 2nd Corps in Italy
1970 Died
Series Description
- Name Card File. (Box No. 1-34.)
  Cards filed by last name alphabetically of Poles who were deported to the Soviet Union during World War II.
- Statements, Reports, Depositions. (Box No. 35-68.)
  Statements, reports, and depositions made by Poles deported to the Soviet Union, to the Polish 2nd Corps Bureau of Documents, arranged by document number. Indeces are located in SUBJECT INDEXES TO DOCUMENTS and CARD INDEXES series.
- Materials Filed by Document Number, 1939-1945. (Box No. 68-76.)
  Typewritten copies of documentation from various sources relating to Poles in the Soviet Union, events in Poland during World War II and conditions in the Soviet Union, collected by the Polish 2nd Corps Bureau of Documents, arranged by document number. No index.
- AKTA WEWNETRZNE BIURA DOKUMENTOW (INTERNAL DOCUMENTS OF THE (Box No. 76-79.)
  Records of the Polish 2nd Corps Bureau of Documents relating to Poles in the Soviet Union and Polish military operations in the Soviet Union, Italy, and the Middle East. Primarily in chronological arrangement. No index.
- Excerpts from Statements by Poles in the Soviet Union, 1940-1943. (Box No. 80-87.)
  English translations of statements made by Poles on conditions in the Soviet Union during their periods of deportation. Arranged by document number. No index.
- Microfiche Copies of Selected Documents. (Box No. 88.)
  Contains copies of documents selected from STATEMENTS, REPORTS, DEPOSITIONS series.
- Subject Index to Documents. (Box No. 89-92.)
  Indexes series of STATEMENTS, REPORTS, DEPOSITIONS.
- Card Indexes. (Box No. 93-109.)
  Card indexes to names of Poles who died or were lost in the Soviet Union, names and locations of forced labor camp, forced labor terms and abbreviations, professional categories of individuals, and to STATEMENTS, REPORTS, DEPOSITIONS series.
- Glass Plate Negatives. (Box No. 110.)
  Negative photographs of Poles in the Soviet Union and scenes in Poland during World War II.
Container List
- PERSONAL CARD INDEX
  - Abeles, Juliusz - Akerman, Lonia (Box 1., Folder 1)
  - Akielan, Jozef - Antczak, Wincenty K. (Folder 2)
  - Antczak, Zofia - Babulski, Stanislaw (Folder 3)
  - Bacik, Roman - Balka, Edward (Folder 4)
  - Baloban, Jan - Baranczyk, Jan (Folder 5)
  - Baranski, Czeslal - Bas, Jan (Folder 6)
  - Basalyk, Helena - Bednarczyk, Julian (Box 2., Folder 1)
  - Bednarek, Tedfil - Bernatowicz, Jan (Folder 2)
  - Bernatowicz, Jaroslaw - Bielhchowicz, Jan (Folder 3)
  - Bielaj, Jan - Bilecki, Michal (Folder 4)
  - Bilek, Romvald - Blawat, Franciszek (Folder 5)
  - Blawat, Irena - Bogdaniec, Jozef (Folder 6)
  - Bagdanowicz, Czeslaw - Bondziul, Konstanty (Box 3., Folder 1)
  - Bongard, Josek - Borycki, P. Pulk. (Folder 2)
  - Boryk, Wawrzyn - Brombosz, Jerzy (Folder 3)
  - Broniatowska, Krystyna - Bugzynski, Kazimierz (Folder 4)
  - Bugzynski, Michal - Bunkiewicz, Jan (Folder 5)
  - Burak, Adam - Byczkowska, Jadwiga (Folder 6)
  - Byk, Roman - Chelminski, Franciszek (Box 4., Folder 1)
  - Chelminski, Moszek - Chodun, Wladyslaw (Folder 2)
  - Chodynaglowacki, Edward - Chronowski, Tadeusz (Folder 3)
  - Chrostowski, Henryk - Ciejko, Jozef (Folder 4)
  - Cieklinska, Lidia - Cybulski, Antoni (Folder 5)
  - Cybulski, Kazimierz - Czaplinski, Jerzy (Folder 6)
  - Czaplinski, Wactaw - Czerkawski, Tadeusz (Box 5., Folder 1)
  - Czerkowski, Adam - Czwalga, Wladyslaw (Folder 2)
  - Czwarnosowna, Irena - Daszkiewicz, Tadeusz (Folder 3)
  - Darbowski, Czeslaw - Demski, Wasyl (Folder 4)
  - Demuth, Franciszek - Dobija, Boleslaw (Folder 5)
  - Dobjasz, Jozef - Domagalski, Wladyslaw (Folder 6)
  - Domaniewska, Ada - Drejza, Wladyslaw (Box 6., Folder 1)
  - Dreksler, Jozef - Dubowska, Janina (Folder 2)
  - Dubowski, Kazimierz - Dybko, Jan (Folder 3)
  - Dybowska, Aniela - Dzigacz, Piotr (Folder 4)
  - Dziegielewski, Kazimierz - Elkau, Dominik (Folder 5)
  - Elkes, Szozana - Fedorowski, Szymon (Folder 6)
  - Feodoryszyn, Maria - Filipowicz, Ryszard (Box 7., Folder 1)
  - Filipowicz, Stanislaw - Fostiak, Roman (Folder 2)
  - Fostyk, Jan - Frycz, Wladyslaw (Folder 3)
  - Fryde, Waclawa - Galinski, Feliks (Folder 4)
  - Galinski, Franciszek - Gastwirth, Mojzesz (Folder 5)
  - Gasztold, Jan - Gebala, Eugeniusz (Folder 6)
  - Gebalik, Nadzieja - Glazer, Michal (Box 8., Folder 1)
  - Glazrot, Szyja - Godlewski, Henryk (Folder 2)
  - Godlewski, Izydor - Golojach, Antoni (Folder 3)
  - Golonski, Bohdan - Goral, Bronislaw (Folder 4)
  - Goralczyk, Franciszek - Graff, Irena (Folder 5)
  - Grafnert, Stanislaw - Grotnik, Eugeniusz (Folder 6)
  - Grott-Nowomiejski, Jan - Grzadziel, Jozef (Box 9., Folder 1)
  - Grzebieniak, Jozef - Gulkowski, Stanislaw (Folder 2)
  - Gumulka, Edward - Hajwentregier, Chaim (Folder 3)
  - Hajzyk, Zdzislaw - Haspod, Wladyslaw (Folder 4)
  - Hass, Juta - Herse, Zofia (Folder 5)
  - Hersz, Edward - Horodyska, Jadwiga (Folder 6)
  - Horodyski, Adam - Hules, Jan (Box 10., Folder 1)
  - Hulewicz, Stefania - Iszkier, Waldo (Folder 2)
  - Itadala, Wojcieck - Jacewicz, Romuald (Folder 3)
  - Jacewicz, Stanislaw - Jakubczyk, Stanislaw (Folder 4)
  - Jakubiak, Jan - Janin, Jozef (Folder 5)
  - Janik, Jozef - Januszewski, Pawel (Folder 6)
  - Januszewski, Witold - Joroszewicz, Jan (Box 11., Folder 1)
  - Jaroszewicz, Kajetan - Jaworska (Jurewicz), Helena (Folder 2)
  - Jaworska, Kazimiera - Jezierski, Rafal (Folder 3)
  - Jezierski, Stanislaw - Jung-Falinska, Anna (Folder 4)
  - Junger, Stefan Kazimierz - Juzyk, Jan (Folder 5)
  - Kabat, Franciszek - Kalimnik, Wlodzimierz (Folder 6)
  - Kalinin, Wlodzimierz - Kaminski, Roman (Box 12., Folder 1)
  - Kaminski, Stanislaw - Karudamski, Lech (Folder 2)
  - Karwowska, Alfreda - Kardasinski, Czeslaw (Folder 3)
  - Kasjanowicz, Bronislaw - Kawik, Jozef (Folder 4)
  - Kawski, Czeslaw - Kipiniak, Adam (Folder 5)
  - Kipp, Waclaw - Kiedel, Michal (Folder 6)
  - Kiryelejza, Leon - Klimkowski, Czeslaw (Box 13., Folder 1)
  - Klimkowski, Mieczyslaw - Knapik, Jozefa (Folder 2)
  - Knapik, Wladyslaw - Koczyk, Franciszek (Folder 3)
  - Kodzio, Feliks - Kolodziej, Stanislaw (Folder 4)
  - Kolodziej, Stanislaw - Konecki, Bronislaw (Folder 5)
  - Konecki, Jozef - Kopec, Wladyslaw (Folder 6)
  - Kopel, Benjamin - Korpanty, Krystyna (Box 14., Folder 1)
  - Korpiena, Szymon - Koszutski, Mikolaj (Folder 2)
  - Koszycki, Jan - Kowalczyk, Stefania (Folder 3)
  - Kowalczyk, Boleslaw - Kowalski, Jozef (Folder 4)
  - Kowalski, Jozef - Kozicz, Ryszard (Folder 5)
  - Koziett, A. - Krajewski, Adam (Folder 6)
  - Krajewska, Wincentyna - Kremer, Wilhelm (Box 15., Folder 1)
  - Krempinski, Michal - Krupa, Michal Kan (Folder 2)
  - Krupa, Michal Sap - Krzosa, Stanislaw (Folder 3)
  - Krzyk, Michal - Kubis, Piotr (Folder 4)
  - Kublicki, Bazyli - Kudrzycki, Antoni (Folder 5)
  - Kudziewicz, Irena - Kulma, Janina (Folder 6)
  - Kulma, Jozef - Kurhan, Jan (Box 16., Folder 1)
  - Kurianowicz, Wlodzimierz - Kuzimowicz, Jan (Folder 2)
  - Kuzio, Franciszek - Lancerer, Natan (Folder 3)
  - Landau, Cwi - Lechowna, Kazimiera (Folder 4)
  - Lecko, Michal - Leszko, Franciszka (Folder 5)
  - Leszko, Tadeusz - Lichota, Julian (Folder 6)
  - Lichtanski, Bronislaw - Lis, Jozef (Box 17., Folder 1)
  - Lis, Regina - Lubanski, Tadeusz (Folder 2)
  - Lubarczyk, Benedykt - Lakomy, Jan (Folder 3)
  - Landuch, Michal - Lobaczewska, Feliksa (Folder 4)
  - Lobaczewski, Aleksander - Lukasiewicz, Stefania (Folder 5)
  - Lukasiewicz, Teodor - Machet, Jozef (Folder 6)
  - Macheta, Antoni - Magiera, Michal (Box 18., Folder 1)
  - Magierowski, Boleslaw - Makarski, Wojciech (Folder 2)
  - Makaruk, Adolf - Malinowski, Karol (Folder 3)
  - Malinowski, Konstanty - Mankowski, Kazimierz (Folder 4)
  - Mankowski, Romuald - Markowski, Stanislaw (Folder 5)
  - Markowski, Tadeusz - Maslanka, Jozef (Folder 6)
  - Maslanka, Jozef - Mazur, Stanislawa (Box 19., Folder 1)
  - Mazur, Szymon - Metelski, Marjan (Folder 2)
  - Meyer, Jerzy - Michniewicz, Antoni (Folder 3)
  - Michniewicz, Feliks - Mikitczuk, Jan (Folder 4)
  - Mikitynowicz, Jan - Minkowski, Paulin (Folder 5)
  - Minkus, Wladyslaw - Moczek, Michal (Folder 6)
  - Moczko, Antoni - Moroz, Dyonizy (Box 20., Folder 1)
  - Moroz, Julian - Mroz, Tadeusz (Folder 2)
  - Mroz, Wladyslaw - Myszkowski, Franciszek (Folder 3)
  - Myszkowski, Jerzy - Nast Wladyslaw (Folder 4)
  - Nastowna, Janina - Niedziulka, Maria (Folder 5)
  - Niedzwiatowska, Stefania - Niwinski, Antoni (Folder 6)
  - Nizelski, Jan - Nowak, Stanislaw (Box 21., Folder 1)
  - Nowak, Stanislaw - Nowosielska, Halina (Folder 2)
  - Nowosielska, Zuzanna - Ogonski, Wladyslaw (Folder 3)
  - Ogorek, Leon - Olizar, Andrej (Folder 4)
  - Olizarowski, Anatol - Orleanski, Kazimierz (Folder 5)
  - Orleanski, Mieczyslaw - Ostrowski, Antoni (Folder 6)
  - Ostrowski, Boleslaw - Pajak, Zofia (Box 22., Folder 1)
  - Pajak, Zbigniew - Para, Mikolaj (Folder 2)
  - Para, Marian - Patipiuk, Stefan (Folder 3)
  - Patkowski, Stanislaw - Pawlowski, Jan (Folder 4)
  - Pawlowski, Jan - Perucki, Piotr (Folder 5)
  - Perun, Roman - Pieczychlebek, Wladyslaw (Folder 6)
  - Pieczygin, Piotr - Pietrzycki, Edward (Box 23., Folder 1)
  - Pietrzykowna, Helena - Piotrowski, Michal (Folder 2)
  - Piotrowski, Rafal - Plichta, Jozef (Folder 3)
  - Plisak, Aleksander - Podolecki, Albin (Folder 4)
  - Podolinski, Jerzy - Pomasowa, Irena (Folder 5)
  - Pomian, Maria - Potopowicz, Henryk (Folder 6)
  - Potorski, Jozef - Pryjomko, Bronislaw (Box 24., Folder 1)
  - Przastek, Stanislaw - Pucharek, Wasyl (Folder 2)
  - Puchera, Jozef - Pyzik, Michalina (Folder 3)
  - Raba, Wladyslaw - Rajchel, Stanislaw (Folder 4)
  - Rajchert, Juda - Rawkuc, Piotr (Folder 5)
  - Rawluk, Franciszek - Rochman, Jakub (Folder 6)
  - Roclawska, Krystyna - Romanowicz, Leokadia (Box 25., Folder 1)
  - Romanowicz, Aleksander - Rozenberg, Maks (Folder 2)
  - Rozenberg, Szmul - Rudnicki, Gracian (Folder 3)
  - Rudnicki, Jozef - Rybak, Aria (Folder 4)
  - Rybak, Jozef - Rysz, Tadeusz (Folder 5)
  - Ryszkowska, Helena - Sadowski, Wladyslaw (Folder 6)
  - Sadowski, Wladyslaw - Sapieja, Tadeusz (Box 26., Folder 1)
  - Saporowski, Jozef - Schenhop, Jozef (Folder 2)
  - Scherer, Zofia - Serwatko, Leonard (Folder 3)
  - Serzysko, Stanislaw - Sienkiewicz, Konstanty (Folder 4)
  - Sienkiewicz, Mieczyslaw - Siwinski, Wladyslaw (Folder 5)
  - Siwko, Jan - Skowronski, Ludwik (Folder 6)
  - Skowronski, Michal - Slotko, Maria (Box 27., Folder 1)
  - Slowicka, Jozefa - Sobiech, Edward (Folder 2)
  - Sobiech, Jozef - Sokolewicz, Jan (Folder 3)
  - Sokol, Helena - Sowinska, Stefania (Folder 4)
  - Sowinski, Aleksander - Staniewicz, Andrzej (Folder 5)
  - Staniewski, Stanislaw - Statkiewicz, Antoni (Folder 6)
  - Statkiewicz, Jozef - Stiel, Zenon (Box 28., Folder 1)
  - Stiepniewski, Jozef - Stryzek, Mac (Folder 2)
  - Stryjek, Stefan - Sulkowski, Jerzy (Folder 3)
  - Sulma, Jan - Szabunio, Stanislaw (Folder 4)
  - Szabunio, Witold - Szatanowna, Genowefa (Folder 5)
  - Szatarski, Jan - Szczypka, Franciszek (Folder 6)
  - Szczyrska, Maria - Szlachetka, Stanislaw (Box 29., Folder 1)
  - Szlachter, Jechil - Szpakowicz, Pawel (Folder 2)
  - Szpakowksi, Adam - Szum, Roman (Folder 3)
  - Szumanski, Adam - Szymanski, Mieczyslaw (Folder 4)
  - Szymanski, Mieczyslaw - Slezak, Jozef (Folder 5)
  - Slimak, Julia - Swierczynski, Klemens (Folder 6)
  - Swierdzewski, Boleslaw - Tarasowicz, Edward (Box 30., Folder 1)
  - Taraszkiewicz, Jan - Tecza, Franciszek (Folder 2)
  - Teczowa, Helena - Tomaszewski, Szczepan (Folder 3)
  - Tomaszewski, Walenty - Trojanowski, Kpt. (Folder 4)
  - Trojanowski, Edward - Tumanowski, Jan (Folder 5)
  - Tumidalski, Jozef - Tyszka, Jan (Folder 6)
  - Tyszkiewicz, Aleksander - Urbanksi, Kesawery (Box 31., Folder 1)
  - Urbanski, Mikolaj - Walczak, Stanislaw (Folder 2)
  - Walczak, Stanislaw - Warszawska, Weronika (Folder 3)
  - Warszawski, Waclaw - Wawrzesta, Franciszek (Folder 4)
  - Wawrzkowicz, Bronislaw - Werynski, Jozef (Folder 5)
  - Weselak, Zofia - Wielgosz, Ludwik (Folder 6)
  - Wieliczker, Maurycy - Wilczynski, Aleksander (Box 32., Folder 1)
  - Wilczynski, Andrzej - Wisniewski, Marcin (Folder 2)
  - Wisniewski, Michal - Wlodek, Zdzislaw (Folder 3)
  - Wlodyka, Tadeusz - Wojtak, Stanislaw (Folder 4)
  - Wojtakowski, Lucjan - Woloch, Jozef (Folder 5)
  - Wolodkowicz, Jozef - Wozniak, Jan (Folder 6)
  - Wozniak, Jan - Wroblewski, Kazimierz (Box 33., Folder 1)
  - Wroblewski, Ludwik - Wywiak, Stanislaw (Folder 2)
  - Zabawa, Rudolf - Zajda, Stanislaw (Folder 3)
  - Zajdel, Henryk - Zaniewski, Tadeusz (Folder 4)
  - Zaniewski, Witold - Zawistowicz, Wanda (Folder 5)
  - Zawistowski, Waclaw - Zglinicki, Marian (Folder 6)
  - Zglinnicki, Aleksander - Zienkiewicz, Adam (Box 34., Folder 1)
  - Zienkiewicz, Antoni - Zulauf, Irena (Folder 2)
  - Zundelewicz, Michal - Zatkowska, Jozefa (Folder 3)
  - Zebracka, Ada - Zurakowski, Antoni (Folder 4)
  - Zuranski, Adam - N.N (Folder 5)
  - N.N. (Folder 6)
  - Volume 1
    - Nos. 5-284 (Box 35., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 290-464 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 465-551 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 566-765 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 767-1230 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 1232-1299 (Folder 6)
  - Volume 2
    - Nos. 1302-1381
    - Nos. 1393-1551 (Box 36., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 1554-1636 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 1638-1685 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 1702-1896 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 1904-2100 (Folder 5)
  - Volume 3
    - Nos. 2101-2237 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 2241-2391 (Folder 7)
    - Nos. 2392-2577 (Box 37., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 2582-3248 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 3257-3582 (Folder 3)
  - Volume 4
    - Nos. 3609-3689 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 3691-4180 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 4215-4486 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 4502-4772 (Folder 7)
    - Nos. 4778-5085 (Box 38., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 5087-5231 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 5286-5397 (Folder 3)
  - Volume 5
    - Nos. 5439-5723 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 5727-6097 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 6102-6214 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 6220-6556 (Folder 7)
    - Nos. 6557-6824 (Box 39., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 6825-7196 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 7251-7486 (Folder 3)
  - Volume 6
    - Nos. 7517-7630 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 7632-7740 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 7746-8005 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 8007-8280 (Folder 7)
    - Nos. 8286-8593 (Box 40., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 8600-8732 (Folder 2)
  - Volume 7
    - Nos. 8669-8826 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 8827-9175 (Folder 4)
  - Volume 7 (Contd.)
    - Nos. 9184-9449 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 9455-9629 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 9637-9717 (Box 41., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 9718-9866 (Folder 2)
  - Volume 8
    - Nos. 9911-10,495 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 10,553-10,623 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 10,643-10,702 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 10,703-10,718 (Folder 6)
  - Volume 9
    - Nos. 10,719-10,744 (Folder 7)
    - Nos. 10,745-10,746 (Box 42., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 10,747-11,112 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 11,113-11,214 (Folder 3)
  - Volume 10
    - Nos. 11,215-11,496 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 11,504-11,653 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 11,654-11,684 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 11,685-11,930 (Box 43., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 11,931-11,962 (Folder 2)
  - Volume 11
    - Nos. 11,965-12,389 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 12,394-12,464 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 12,465-12,543 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 12,544-12,580 (Folder 6)
  - Volume 12 (Box 44.)
    - Nos. 12,581-12,637 (Folder 1)
    - Nos. 12,639-12,695 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 12,696-12,805 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 12,806-12,850 (Folder 4)
  - Volume 13
    - Nos. 12,851-13,972 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 13,973-13,974 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 13,975-14,032 (Folder 7)
    - Nos. 14,034-14,230 (Box 45., Folder 1)
  - Volume 14
    - Nos. 14,231-14,276 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 14,277-14,321 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 14,322-14,450 (Folder 4)
  - Volume 15
    - Nos. 14,451-14,461 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 14,462-14,472 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 14,473-15,52 (Folder 7)
    - Nos. 15,527-15,570 (Box 46., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 15,581-15,716 (Folder 2)
- REPORTS
  - Volume 16
    - Nos. 1-130 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 131-276 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 277-400 (Folder 5)
  - Volume 17
    - Nos. 401-559 (Box 47., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 560-700 (Folder 2)
  - Volume 18
    - Nos. 701-865 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 866-1,026 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 1,028-1,100 (Folder 5)
  - Volume 19
    - Nos. 1,101-1,344 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 1,345-1,550 (Box 48., Folder 1)
  - Volume 20
    - Nos. 1,552-1,729 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 1,730-1,900 (Folder 3)
  - Volume 21
    - Nos. 1,901-2,105 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 2,106-2,350 (Folder 5)
  - Volume 22
    - Nos. 2,351-2,500 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 2,501-2,631 (Box 49., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 2,632-2,750 (Folder 2)
  - Volume 23
    - Nos. 2,751-2,905 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 2,906-3,058 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 3,059-3,150 (Folder 5)
  - Volume 24
    - Nos. 3,151-3,292 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 3,293-3,464 (Folder 7)
    - Nos. 3,465-3,550 (Box 50., Folder 1)
  - Volume 25
    - Nos. 3,551-3,747 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 3,748-3,900 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 3,901-4,000 (Folder 4)
  - Volume 26
    - Nos. 4,001-4,126 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 4,127-4,277 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 4,278-4,400 (Folder 7)
  - Volume 27
    - Nos. 4,401-4,559 (Box 51., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 4,560-4,750 (Folder 2)
  - Volume 28
    - Nos. 4,751-4,908 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 4,909-5,079 (Folder 4)
    - Nos. 5,080-5,149 (Folder 5)
  - Volume 29
    - Nos. 5,151-5,328 (Folder 6)
    - Nos. 5,329-5,500 (Box 52., Folder 1)
  - Volume 30
    - Nos. 5,501-5,560 (Folder 2)
    - Nos. 5,651-5,813 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 5,814-5,900 (Folder 4)
  - Volume 31
    - Nos. 5,901-6,128 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 6,129-6,300 (Folder 6)
  - Volume 32
    - Nos. 6,301-6,484 (Box 53., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 6,485-6,550 (Folder 2)
  - Volume 33
    - Nos. 6,551-6,730 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 6,731-6,850 (Folder 4)
  - Volume 34
    - Nos. 6,851-6,995 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 6,996-7,150 (Folder 6)
  - Volume 35
    - Nos. 7,151-7,291 (Box 54., Folder 1)
    - Nos. 7,292-7,500 (Folder 2)
  - Volume 36
    - Nos. 7,501-7,669 (Folder 3)
    - Nos. 7,671-7,899 (Folder 4)
  - Volume 37
    - Nos. 7,901-8,048 (Folder 5)
    - Nos. 8,049-8,250 (Box 55., Folder 1)
  - Volume 38